[{"id": 1590, "question": "The college entrance exam is not only a big challenge for Chinese high school students, but also a very important exam in the lives of South Korean students. Although the long, cold winter has already started in South Korea, the annual national exams have made the atmosphere very heated. More than 675,000 South Korean high school graduates took the college entrance exam last Wednesday. They usually take exams in Korean, maths, sociology , history and foreign languages. Officially there is one college place for every 1.33 students. But because all the students want to go to the top universities in the country, the competition can reach one place for 10 students. The students want to attend these colleges for both their famous names and better job opportunities. Because students face fierce ...\n\nQ: What do we know about South Korean annual national exams?", "options": ["Senior 3 students have to compete fiercely because there is only one place for 10 students.", "Senior 3 students have to stay long into night at school.", "Many of the Senior 3 students can't have enough sleep.", "Airplanes are ordered to avoid landing and take-off during national exams."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1514, "question": "2016 International Summer School The 2016 University of Cambridge International Summer Schools will run in Cambridge from 6 July to 22 August 2016. Our programs give you the opportunity to meet award-winning lecturers, stay and dine in one of the historic Cambridge Colleges and enjoy a range of weekend excursions and social activities. To sign up for a program simply apply online, or download an application form from our website. Places on courses and in-college accommodation are limited, so we encourage applicants to apply early to avoid disappointment. This year we will be offering specialist programs in: Ancient Empires, Literature, History, Medieval Studies and new for 2016, Creative Writing and Hanseatic League. If you are looking to study a number of different subject areas, the Inte...\n\nQ: What should people do if they want to sign up for a program in this ad?", "options": ["They should go to Cambridge by plane.", "They should phone Cambridge.", "They should call for an application form.", "They should apply for the program online."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 492, "question": "WILD WEATHERMAN Name: Sam Champion Hot job: TV Weatherman Where: ABC-TV, New York City When you were a child, did you plan to forecast wind, rain, and snow on TV? I wanted to be a foreign journalist. I took courses in weather science at Eastern Kentucky University, but I majored in broadcasting news. How did you finally become a weatherman? My first job in the early 1980s was at the local TV station in Paducah, Kentucky. I did everything from turning on the lights in the morning to writing and delivering morning news. I put together weather forecasts, and became interested in them. Back then, how did you forecast weather? Independent companies collected computer information that showed, for example, how a single weather system might split into snow or snow mixed with rain. The information ...\n\nQ: The study of weather science is called   _   .", "options": ["meteorology", "forecasting", "geography", "Earth science"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1639, "question": "Have you ever tried broccoli ice cream? That's what Oliver serves his customers in the new movie Oliver's Organic Ice Cream. The one-minute film was created by kids. A film is a movie. The young students learned their moviemaking skills at the Jacob Burns Film Center. The center is in Pleasantville, New York. Kids who go there learn how to make movies and music videos. The character Oliver and his treats are animated. In an animated movie, objects, such as ice cream and paper dolls, appear to be alive or moving. Animated movies are made up of hundreds of pictures. It takes 15 pictures to make just one second of film. To make a movie that lasts one minute, students need to take about 900 frames. A frame is a picture. Animation expert Joe Summerhays teaches kids the steps to shoot a movie. H...\n\nQ: We can infer that Oliver is probably a(n)   _  .", "options": ["moviemaker", "movie character", "farmer", "animation expert"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 447, "question": "Good Teachers A language training school at Yayuncun needs two full-time teachers and three part-time teachers to teach adults, 12 students a class, oral English and business English during afternoons and evenings. Full-time teachers 25--30 hours per week, 10 000--2 000 yuan per month. Part-time teachers can choose the class to teach, 100--150 yuan per hour, according to your experience. Need native English speakers with teaching experience. Please send your RESUME and PICTURE to eslchina@ yahoo.com.cn Writers/Researchers Currently, Fisher's Travel SOS is looking for the freelance writer and researcher with experience in journalism and the ability to computers, it is part-time positions for our project that will take a month to complete. Work is conducted at home, and will take a couple of...\n\nQ: You must know English if you want to be  _", "options": ["a teacher", "a waiter", "a writer", "a seller"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1408, "question": "Rob Coulter worked in the wild of South Africa. He knew the animals, insects, and reptiles of Africa very well. Rob knew them so well that he became careless. One night, while camping alone, Rob reached out to pick up a large piece of wood and felt something bite his arm. Rob didn't think much about it. But a little later, his arm began to ache. When he looked closely at it, he immediately saw two teeth marks in the skin of his arm. He realized that a poisonous snake had bitten him. His pulse became rapid. Rob's mind raced as he thought about what he had to do to survive. Rob knew that he should remain calm, stay still, keep the injured arm below the level of his heart and avoid eating or drinking anything, especially anything with alcohol in it. He also knew that cutting the wound to suck...\n\nQ: How can we deal with snake wounds according to the passage?", "options": ["Stay calm and don't move.", "Run for help as fast as possible.", "Drink alcohol to stop the poison.", "Cut the wound and suck the poison out."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1428, "question": "Money spent on advertising is money spent as well as any I know of.It serves directly to assist a rapid distribution of goods at reasonable prices, thereby establishing a firm home market and so making it possible to provide for export at competitive prices.By drawing attention to new ideas it helps enormously to raise standards of living.By helping to increase demand it ensures an increased need for labour, and is therefore an effective way to fight unemployment.It lowers the costs of many services: without advertisements your daily newspaper would cost four times as much, the price of your television license would need to be doubled, and travel by bus or tube would cost 20 per cent more. And perhaps most important of all, advertising provides a guarantee of reasonable value in the produc...\n\nQ: The author thinks that the well-known TV personality   _  .", "options": ["forces his own views on the public", "holds one-sided views on advertising", "can't tell persuasion from information", "is interested in nothing but the buyers' attention"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2071, "question": "Five-year-old Jocelyn Rojas spent all day playing happily with her friends outside her grandmother's apartment building. Her mom, Jaimee, kept her eye on the little girl from a window. At about 4 p.m., Jocelyn walked around the corner of the building to get her bicycle. However, half an hour later, she disappeared. Jaimee called 911. A short time later, police officers and firefighters crowded inthe area, blocking streets and searching the neighborhood. Officers handed out photos of the girl wearing thick-framed glasses. Temar Boggs, 15, a school athlete in track, was with some friends moving a couch into the apartment of his elderly neighbor when one officer approached him and asked if he'd seen Jocelyn. Unfortunately, none of them had seen her. A little bit later, Temar and his friends w...\n\nQ: What was Temar doing when the police were searching for Jocelyn?", "options": ["He and his friends were playing outside the building.", "He was helping the police hand out the photos of the missing girl.", "He and his friends were helping his neighbor moving a couch.", "He and his friends were having a cycling race."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3216, "question": "Researchers in the psychology department at the University of California at Los Angeles (UCLA) have discovered a major difference in the way men and women respond to stress. This difference may explain why men are more likely to suffer from stress-related disorders. Until now, psychological research has maintained that both men and women have the same \"fight-or-flight\" reaction to stress. In other words, individuals either react with aggressive behavior, such as verbal or physical conflict (\"fight\"), or they react by withdrawing from the stressful situation (\"flight\"). However, the UCLA research team found that men and women have quite different biological and behavioral responses to stress. While men often react to stress in the fight-or-flight response, women often have another kind of r...\n\nQ: What can be learned from the passage?", "options": ["Male hormones help build up the body's resistance to stress.", "In a family a mother cares more about children than a father does.", "Biological differences lead to different behavioral responses to stress.", "The UCLA study was designed to confirm previous research findings."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1750, "question": "Where is that noise coming from? Not sure? Try living with your eyes closed for a few years. Blind people are better at locating sounds than people who can see, a new study says, without the benefits of vision the ears seem to work much better. Previous studies have shown that blind people are better than others at reaching out and touching the sources of sounds that are close by. Researchers from the University of Montreal wanted to see if blind people were also better at locating sounds that are far away. Twenty-three blind people participated in the study. All had been sightless for at least 20 years. Fourteen of them had lost their vision before age 11. the rest went blind after age 16. The experiment also included 10 people who could see but were wearing blind-folds. In one task, volu...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the passage?", "options": ["Whether to be able to locate the sounds can be of vital importance for the blind.", "All the volunteers in the experiment are sightless.", "All the participants did equally well when picking sounds from whatever direction.", "The later people become blind, the better they can perform in telling the direction of sound"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2341, "question": "Whales live in the ocean, but they are not fish. They are warm-blooded mammals and must have air to breathe. The babies are born alive and drink milk from the mother's body. It took millions of years for the whale to develop as it is today. Every spring groups of whales swim hundreds of kilometers to warm places to bear their young. Each group goes to the same place every year. The mothers take very good care of their babies. The fully grown whales are very gentle and playful with each other, and with humans. They \"talk\" to each other with a high noise that sounds beautiful. This\"talking\" can be heard for more than 300 kilometers in open waters. Yet humans kill over a hundred whales a day. They kill them to make whale oils and a lot of other things. Killing them is a modern business with m...\n\nQ: When whales talk, it sounds like    _   .", "options": ["talking", "whispering", "quarreling", "singing"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1848, "question": "Table manners are very different in every country. For example, when you are in England you must not lift your soup plate to your mouth. This is very impolite. But when you are in Japan this is completely normal. Lifting your plate to your mouth in Japan is a traditional way of drinking your soup. And also in Japan you don't have to worry about making a noise when you drink it. It just shows that you really like the food! But it is not the same in Britain, so you shouldn't make a noise when eating there. In Britain, people don't put their hands or arms on the table during the meal. But in Mexico, guests keep their hands on the table all the time. In fact, you should watch what your hands do very carefully. In Arab countries, it is impolite when you eat with your left hand, so don't do it! ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE according to the text?", "options": ["Keeping your hands on the table is polite in Britain but impolite in Mexico.", "In Arab countries you should eat with your right hand.", "Speaking when you're eating is impolite just in some cultures.", "In Ukraine, it's a tradition that the guest eats first."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2162, "question": "*1. Malan Flower: China Children's Art Theatre stages a fairy tale musical \"Malan Flower\" this weekend. Beautiful Malan flowers were blossoming everywhere on Malan Mountain, and hard-working girl Xiao Lan was married to the god of flowers, Ma Lang. They lived a happy life in harmony with Grandpa Tree. and all the lovely little animals. However, greedy Old Cat made use of the jealousy of elder sister Da Lan to kill Xiao Lan, in an attempt to keep the magic Malan flower under her possession. This fairy tale entertained three generations of Chinese youth. Time: 7: 30 p. m., until August 21 Place: The Great Theatre of the Cultural Palace of the Nationalities, west of Xidan Area Tel: 6602-2530 *2. Joyful jugglers: The China Acrobatic Troupe is staging a nightly variety show at the Tiandi Theatr...\n\nQ: What phone number should you dial for further information if you are a pop song fan?", "options": ["6602-2530.", "6502-3984.", "6835-4055.", "8403-3500."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1208, "question": "It was 9:00 am already! Richard had to leave for work! Before leaving he hurriedly looked at the newspaper and stood still! Is he seeing it right? He rubbed his eyes and saw again... Yes, it was his name in the obituary ! He threw the paper in the bin and screamed. Richard started to recollect. He remembered that last night when he went to bed he had a chest pain and he was rushed to hospital. Then he went into a sound sleep. But what happened after that? He could suddenly see his living room filled with people... all in tears; his mom, his wife and his children. He also saw his best friend, the one he had a serious misunderstanding a few days back. He wanted to say \"Sorry\" to him... but now no one could hear his voice. He wondered how he could tell his mom that he felt so thankful to have...\n\nQ: The writer of the story mainly tells us that   _  .", "options": ["misunderstanding between friends is common", "we need to see a doctor when having a chest pain", "getting along well with friends is important", "we should tell our family how much we love them"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1840, "question": "One rainy night , Mark decided to end his life . Having undergone a lot of sufferings and frustrations , he walked the streets , feeling desperate . On that same night , I was sitting in my room when I heard the doorbell rang . My mom opened the door , finding herself face-to-face with a very disheveled-looking man , Mark , with tears running down his face . My mom , overcome by pity , invited him inside . Curious , I went downstairs to get a better look . The sight of the man , holding his head in his hands and crying , made my chest ache . I raced back upstairs to my room , pulled out my only half-dollar coin from my money jar and ran back downstairs . When I reached the door of the living room , I walked right in and quickly made my way over to the stranger . I put the half-dollar in hi...\n\nQ: Why did Mark cry when he tightly held the coin ?", "options": ["Because he realized he was not abandoned by the world .", "Because he was worried about whether he could pay it back .", "Because he finally got money when he was in great need of it .", "Because he felt ashamed that he should get money from a child ."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1516, "question": "Women had a significant part to play during World War II,which was the time when women also made their own contributions.Some women's great efforts and their names have been recorded in history.Here's a look at some of the strong figures of women in World War II. Tatiana Nikolaevna Baramzina was born in Glazov of Russia on December 12,1919.In 1943,she was sent to the Central Women's Sniper Training School and upon her graduation in April,she was further sent to the front.She managed to kill around 16 enemies in the first three months!Unfortunately,she was captured by the enemies and was killed on the fifth of July in 1944.Today,the street where she grew up has been renamed in her memory. Anne Frank was a Germanborn Jewish girl who was wellknown for the publication of her diary that describ...\n\nQ: What is mainly discussed in the text?", "options": ["Women were braver than men in World War II.", "Women and men made equal contributions in World War II.", "Women played a significant role in World War II.", "Women's death rate was high in World War II."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2692, "question": "Teresa was born in Yugoslavia on August 27,1910. Her parents were Albanians and member of the Roman Catholic Church. When she was seven years old, her father was murdered. She decided not to be filled with hate because of this tragedy . Instead, she would seek a life of love. This ambition led her to Ireland where she became a nun at the age of eighteen. After only one year of training, she was sent to India to teach in a school called Loretto House, where the students were mostly from rich Indian families. After 15 years there, she left her duties as a teacher to \"follow Christ into the slums .\" Her heart led her away from the rich to the needs of the poor. She was then 36 years old. Teresa no longer was affiliated with the Irish nuns who sent her to Loreto House but worked independently....\n\nQ: Perhaps the most important lesson the world has learned from Mother Teresa is  _  .", "options": ["regular assistance", "food and shelter", "to care for the poor of the earth", "protection"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1217, "question": "The word I'm going to introduce to you today is-phubbing. Let's see the definition of this term:phubbing n. the act of snubbing someone in a social setting by looking at your cell phone instead of paying attention As you can probably guess, phubbing is a blend of phone and snubbing. The term was coined by a 23-year-old Melbourne resident Alex Haigh. Obviously, he got fed up with how people are always checking Facebook or Twitter on their phones when they are supposed to be interacting with someone face to face. He wanted to put an end to this social phenomenon, therefore he came up with this catchy term. And it did catch on. The word's earliest media mention dates back to June 2012, and in a little over a year's time, phubbing has already been picked up by almost all the mainstream media o...\n\nQ: This passage is mainly talking about   _  .", "options": ["the rise of phubbing in all the mainstream media outlets", "a new term \"phubbing\"and its problem", "the campaign of keeping phubbing", "different opinions on phubbing"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2989, "question": "Hidden in a small street in the south end of Springfield, not far from buildings torn apart by the tornado earlier this year, Frigo's is an Italian restaurant right in our own backyard. Frigo's is not a tiny place. It provides different kinds of Italian food. There are refrigerator cases full of prepared foods and desserts, and shelves filled with olives and various pasta. There's some traditional Italian music and the smell is of olive oil and garlic . Above the largest refrigerator case, there's a chalk board covered with desriptions of more Italian sandwiches than I could remember. I stepped into Frigo's almost by accident when I had to stay in Springfield into the evening for an open house at the school where I work. Frigo's is the perfect place to find something quick to go. There are...\n\nQ: How much did the writer pay for his first meal at Frigo's?", "options": ["$4.75", "$5.25", "$9.74", "$4.99"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 171, "question": "China has recently been faced with serious issues of product safety. In Panama, it is said that medicine made with a poisonous chemical sickened some people. A Chinese company had identified it as diethylamide glycol ( []), a low - cost substitute commonly used in automobile antifreeze . Some countries have banned Chinese-made toothpaste containing diethylamide glycol. China has now told companies to discontinue its use, even though it says the toothpaste is safe. Another industrial chemical, melamine, was found in wheat flour used to make pet food in North America. Thousands of dogs and cats became sick. The United States has restricted some imports of Chinese seafood because they contained banned substance. And questions have been raised about other products, including children's toys co...\n\nQ: How many cases with safety problems are mentioned in the passage?", "options": ["Six", "Five", "Four", "Three"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2806, "question": "Today's museums include plenty of high culture, but you can still find shrines to the extraordinary. Here's a look at five curious museum stops across Canada. Vancouver Police Museum The setting, terrible enough, is the old Coroner's Court and forensics lab, including the morgue(room where dead bodies are kept). Artifacts, from the 1870s on, include badges, uniforms, police equipment, items from criminals, and even preserved organs--all in all an arresting experience. Vulcan Tourism & Trek Station Designed to resemble a spacecraft, the Treck Station celebrates Vulcan's coincidental relationship to Mr. Spock's planet, Go to a building that features an 800-piece collection of Star Trek memorabilia -- including Spock's ears and floor-to-ceiling space paintings. If you want to know more about ...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that the ancestors of accordion originated in  _  .", "options": ["Canada", "America", "Asia", "Africa"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 896, "question": "Do you want to write your password down so that no one can see it, or do you want to send someone a secret message? Knowing how to make an invisible ink message will have you feeling like a secret agent in no time. These are instructions for making invisible ink using baking soda. Difficulty: Easy Time required: A few minutes What you need: Baking soda, Paper, Water, Light bulb, Paintbrush, Measuring cup, Purple grape juice Here's how: There are at least two methods of using baking soda as invisible ink. Mix equal amounts of water and baking soda. Use a paintbrush to write a message onto white paper, using the baking soda solution as \"ink\". Allow the ink to dry. One way to read the message is to hold the paper up to a heat source, such as a light bulb. The baking soda will cause the writin...\n\nQ: How can you read the message in invisible ink easily?", "options": ["read it in the daytime", "read it near a heater", "Put it in hot water", "put it in a fridge"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 652, "question": "Lee Ann Laraway has polio and is not able to move very much. Most things are out of reach for her. Jeannie, a Labrador retriever, acts as her arms and legs. Jeannie understands 72 or more different commands. On a shopping trip, she can get money for Lee Ann at the bank or candies at the store. She can pay the cashier and get change back. Jeannie brings things to Lee Ann and puts them in her lap. Jeannie was trained at a place called Canine Companions for Independence, located on twelve acres of land in Santa Rosa (California). The land was donated by the cartoonist Charles Shultz. \"We train four different types of dogs here,\" said Ken Kirsh, a dog trainer there. \"Hearing dogs, service dogs, skilled companion dogs, and facility dogs.\" Trainers work with Labrador retrievers and golden retrie...\n\nQ: People want to talk to Noah mainly because  _  .", "options": ["he is good at training dogs", "he is not only honest but also lovely", "they want to play with his dog", "they want to ask him for help"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2483, "question": "We live in a dangerous world. The figures for crime go up year by year. If you were attacked in the street, would you be able to defend yourself? Not very well probably, especially if someone was pointing a gun at you. We all see a lot of violence of films, but recently some programs on television showed how people can defend themselves without guns. For example, in one film a woman was attacked from behind. She threw the man, who was heavier and stronger than she was, over her head. Then she held him tightly on the ground. How? She knew Judo. Jiu-jitsu, as judo is sometimes called, means \"muscle science\" in Japanese. The student of judo needs to learn a lot about the body, its bones and muscles. Judo uses a number of \"falls\", \"holds\" and \"throws\". Someone who does not know judo cannot def...\n\nQ: What's the best title for this short passage?", "options": ["How to defend oneself", "Violence in films", "How to practise judo", "Something about judo"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2388, "question": "After two classes, I started to recognize several of the faces in each class. There was always someone braver than the others who would introduce themselves and ask me questions about how I was liking Forks. I tried to be , so mostly I just lied a lot to appear to be skilled at dealing with people. At least I never needed the map. One girl sat next to me in both Trig and Spanish, and she walked with me to the cafeteria for lunch. She was tiny, several inches shorter than my five feet four inches, but her wildly curly dark hair made up a lot of the difference between our heights. I couldn't remember her name, so I smiled and nodded as she gossiped about teachers and classes. I didn't try to keep up. We sat at the end of a full table with several of her friends, who she introduced to me. I f...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which statement is NOT true?", "options": ["The girl walked with \"me\" was a little short.", "\"I\" saw the five students for the first time.", "Those students sitting in the corner had finished their food.", "\"I\" probably wanted to know more about those five students."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1925, "question": "Ad.1 West High School Bake Sale Come and support our band and buy some delicious baked goods! Friday, September 20th, 2:00 - 4:00 p.m. In the hall by the office after school Cookies: 25 cents each or 5 for $1 Brownies: 50 cents each or 3 for $1.25 Cake by the slice: $1 Whole cakes: $8 Proceeds go toward sending our band to Nationals. Ad.2 SHIPPING AND HANDLING CHARGES Ups or U.S. Parcel Post are the standard methods for continental U.S. shipments. ORDER TOTAL GROUND EXPEDITED GROUND 9-12 working days 4-5 working days $0.00 to $30.00 $4.50 $5.50 $30.01 to $60.00 $7.25 $8.25 $60.01 to $100.00 $9.50 $10.50 $100.01 to $200.00 $11.50 $12.50 Add $7.00 to Ground Rates for 3 Days....\n\nQ: How much should you pay for an order totaling $50 for the expedited ground  ?", "options": ["$1", "$7.25", "$8.25", "$15.5"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1810, "question": "A 13-year-old American boy on Saturday became the youngest climber to conquer Mount Everest, the world's highest mountain. Jordan Romero from Big Bear, California, climbed up the 8,850-meter summit from the Tibetan side. On the same day, a Nepali man, Apa Sherpa, broke his own world record of climbing Everest when he reached the summit for the twentieth time. Apa Shepa's team set off from Nepal's capital, Kathmandu, last month, heading for the base camp on the Chinese side of the mountain. \"The team has just called in and believe that they are standing on top of Mt. Everest,\" Romero's blog said. \"Their dreams have now come true. Everyone is happy.\" The climbing has put Romero one step closer to reaching his goal of climbing the highest mountains on all seven continents . \"It is just a goal...\n\nQ: Jordan Romero climbed up Mount Everest mainly to   _  .", "options": ["meet Apa Sherpa", "build his body", "break the world record", "realize part of his goal"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1473, "question": "Wal-Mart is not just the world's largest retailer . It's the world's largest company, which sells in three months what number-two retailer Home Depot sells in a year. Wal-Mart exercises its power for just one purpose: to bring the lowest possible prices to its customers. At Wal-Mart, that goal is never reached. The retailer has a clear policy for suppliers: On basic products that don't change, the price Wal-Mart will pay, and will charge shoppers, must drop year after year. But what almost no one outside the world of Wal-Mart and none of its 21,000 suppliers know is the high cost of those low prices. To survive in the face of its pricing demands, makers of everything from bikes to jeans have had to close US plants in favor of obtaining products from abroad. Indeed, the real story of Wal-Ma...\n\nQ: What's the best title for the passage?", "options": ["The Fortune Wal-Mart Makes", "The Wal-Mart you don't Know", "The Biggest Retailer--Wal-Mart", "The Money Saving Tip in Wal-Mart"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3341, "question": "(Reuters)The Thunderbird is one of the most readily recognized creatures of American Indian mythology.While the vast majority of biologists believe the Thunderbird myth to be nothing more than a spiritual symbol, some zoologists believe that the hard may actually exist. I still vividly recall seeing an impossibly large raptor when I was five years old, which a few people have said might be the Thunderbird.Standing in my grandmother's back yard in Alabama, I recall watching an enormous black bird with a swallow - like tail flying directly over me from an oak tree. Its wingspan seemed to be at least three times my height, which would have made it at least fourteen feet across. While the early childhood memory is often unreliable, I clearly remember the details of the \"Thunderbird\".To this ve...\n\nQ: How is the passage mainly organized?", "options": ["By giving examples.", "By following time order", "By making comparisons.", "By presenting a general idea."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1014, "question": "BEIJING--Seven prestigious universities in China announced Sunday that they would begin using the same independent exam --besides the national one --to test students hoping to gain entrance to them in 2011. The seven are Peking University, Beihang University, Beijing Normal University, Nankai University, Fudan University, Xiamen University and Hong Kong University. Students who want to gain entrance to any of the seven universities will only have to sit one independent exam, according to the joint announcement. \"This will help lighten the students' load, otherwise they must take several exams for different universities ,\"said the announcement. Passing the exam could result in more than one interview chance, giving the students more opportunities to choose their favorite universities. China...\n\nQ: What's the purpose of students sitting one independent exam to gain entrance to the seven universities?", "options": ["It can reduce students' load to take several exams.", "The universities will have the same standard to test students.", "There will be less trouble marking students' test papers.", "It can avoid fierce competition among these universities."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2375, "question": "Take That Tiger Mom In the ongoing battle between Tiger Moms, French Mamas, and everyone else who wants to know what is the best way to raise their kids, a new study adds evidence that the extreme Tiger-style may do more harm than good. Authoritarian parents are more likely to end up with disrespectful children with violent behaviors, the study found, compared to parents who listen to their kids with the goal of gaining trust. It was the first study to look at how parenting styles affect the way teens view their parents and, in turn, how they behave. The study considered three general styles of parenting. Authoritative parents are demanding and controlling while also being warm and sensitive to their children's needs. Authoritarian parents, on the contrary, are demanding and controlling wi...\n\nQ: According to the passage, children are more likely to obey the rules when   _  .", "options": ["their parents listen to them totally", "they believe in and accept their parents", "their parents are sensitive to their needs", "their parents demand and control their behaviors"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1697, "question": "These days,when about 10.3 million.Americans are jobless and countless mole worry they will be,lovers of yoga are eager to keep peace by twisting their bodies. \"People want to do something relaxing and physically active.My experience is that attendance In classes gone significantly up in the past few months,\"said yoga instructor David,who turned to teaching yoga when his advertising jobs dried up in the recession of 2001.He admitted his private custoIlll~I'8 have fallen off a bit,but \"generally,my long--term private clients are financially well-off and eager to recommend me to their friends.\" \"We've added yoga classes,\"said Nicole Moke,spokeswoman for the fitness centers.\"We add classes every January.\" And if the attack of hard times should fall upon their weft-heeled member ship? \"We've a...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the passage?", "options": ["Meditation classes have been added to attract customers.", "Some yoga instructors will lose their jobs in the hard times.", "The well-heeled membership will be affected in the hard times.", "People practice yoga because they are afraid of being jobless."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 971, "question": "You have heard of Webster Toys. Webster's have made good, safe, interesting toys for more than a hundred years. Now we sell them, and children play with them, in countries fromprefix = st1 /New ZealandtoNorway, and fromJapantoBrazil. We are looking for someone to sell our toys in the Far East. He (or she) will be between the ages of thirty and forty. He will already have some years of selling in world markets behind him. He will speak good English, and at least one other language of the Far East. The person we are looking for will live inSingapore, and work in our office there, but he will travel for up to six months in any one year. He will know the Far East quite well already. He will know how to sell in old markets and where to find new ones. He will understand money and make more than ...\n\nQ: \"Someone who can stand on his own feet\" means   _  .", "options": ["someone who does not stand on others' feet", "someone who can understand money", "someone who can work by himself", "someone who understand many language"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 593, "question": "In most of the time, I am devoted to my research in the lab with my friend Dave, who loves traveling very much. To make our life colorful and relax ourselves, in July, my friend and I are taking a camping trip. We will travel for four weeks and will tour the United States and part of Canada. We have decided to camp because it does not cost as much as vacationing in hotels. We have to plan very carefully in advance. First, the car we are going to drive is very small, so we have decided to take only one small suitcase each and as few camping things as possible. We will take some medicine with us to prevent insects from hurting us, and also food for picnics. Second, there is a lot to see in the United States and Canada, so we have to decide on the direction we want to drive. The date we are l...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is possibly true?", "options": ["They are now on the trip", "They are going to make a tour all over the U.S and Canada.", "They are quite rich.", "July is drawing near."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 724, "question": "Many people write to newspapers and magazines to express their opinions. Letters to the editor must carry the writer's full name, address and telephone number, although the information is not necessary for publication. This requirement to provide personal particulars is a clear indication that writers are responsible for what they say. When a writer wants his voice heard, he needs to claim ownership of his voice. Responsibility is the name of the game. \"People today prefer living together to putting their signatures on a marriage certificate because they refuse to accept responsibility for the relationship,\" said social worker Ken Yip, \"and this is what is causing a lot of family problems.\" When we sign a paper, for example, a business contract or a bank document, the signature is a seal o...\n\nQ: Some people don't want their names known because they are  _  .", "options": ["ready for involvement", "hesitant to make a donation", "afraid of an accusation", "unwilling to draw public attention"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2144, "question": "Skin - diving is a new sport today. This sport takes you into a wonderful new world. It is like a visit to the moon. When you are under water, it is easy for you to climb big rocks because you are no longer heavy .Here, under water, everything is blue and green. During the day, there is plenty of light. When fish swim nearby, you can catch them with your hands.When you have tanks of air on your back, you can stay in deep water for a long time. But you must be careful when you dive in deep water. To catch fish is one of the most interesting parts of this sport. Besides, there are more uses for skin - diving. You can clean ships without taking them out of water. You can get many things from the deep sea. Now you see that skin -diving is both useful and interesting....\n\nQ: With tanks of air on your back, you can  _  .", "options": ["catch fish very easily", "stay under water for a long time", "climb big rocks", "have more fun"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 498, "question": "Every spring Beijing is choked by huge sandstorms.The sky turns a strange and frightening yellow colour as clouds of sand sweep down from the deserts of Mongolia and north-western China.Strong winds blow up the dust and cover everything in sight--in 2006,a storm dumped 330,000 tonnes of dust on Beijing in one night. The number of sandstorms has grown alarmingly over the years as the deserts have expanded.This is partly man-made and partly because of climate .Many grasslands have been overgrazed by sheep and goats,or ploughed up,leaving the soil dangerously exposed.Too much water has been taken out of rivers,and the situation is made worse by increasingly long-lasting droughts that have affected the northern half of China as the climate grows warmer and drier.The result is probably the wors...\n\nQ: At what speed do the nearest sand dunes move towards Beijing according to the passage?", "options": ["More than 15 km a year.", "More than 2 km a month.", "More than 2 km a year.", "More than 15 km a month."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1784, "question": "The father's role in the family is important. One researcher says babies cared for by their fathers have greater cognitive development at one year of age than babies not cared for by their fathers. Another expert reports that by spending time with their pre-school children, fathers can help to develop children's language ability. Researchers also point out that for school-age children, fathers are one link with the outside world. Fathers who value education have children who do better in school than those children whose fathers don't value education. What's more, fathers who spend quality time with their children may give their children happy memories which may last a lifetime. While each father is a unique person who educates children in his own style, good fathers have something in commo...\n\nQ: According to the passage, fathers' involvement in their children's lives may NOT result in    _   .", "options": ["the good fate of their children", "better reading levels of their children", "happy memories which may last a lifetime", "greater cognitive development of their children"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2310, "question": "For years, I thought that my mother would become a Centenarian , but after 98 years and eight months, she recently died of old age. As it was with my father, her funeral took place in the most peaceful setting of the countryside of rural Washington County. Even after my father died, we continued to think of our parents as one. They were a team in the traditional sense. Church and family were their life- lines. They worked hard, never complaining. They expected to earn their daily bread by the sweat of their brow. Once during a conversation with Tom Brokaw, who wrote the best- selling hook The Greatest Generation, I told him, \"You left out my parents.\" They didn't go off to war, but they belonged to the Greatest Generation. They, too, were part of the foundation that made America truly grea...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Mother played a great pan in the family.", "Mother died at the age of 98 years old.", "Mother was buried by the side of father.", "Mother survived father by many years."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1035, "question": "I was now in my twenty third year of residence in this island and was accustomed to the place and to the manner of living. If it had not been the savages who had come to the place to disturb me, I could have been content to spent the rest of my time there, even to the last moment, till I had laid me down and died, like the old goat in the cave. I had also arrived to some little recreations and amusements, which made the time pass more pleasantly with me a great deal than it did before. At first, I had taught my Poll to speak. And he did it so familiarly and talked so clearly and plain that it was very pleasant to me. And he lived with me no less than twenty six years. How long he might live afterwards, I don't know; though I know they have an idea in Brazil that they live a hundred years. ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following statements is true?", "options": ["Robin's dog may be still alive on the island.", "Robin Crusoe lived in harmony with savages.", "Robin Crusoe met an English man while on the island.", "Parrots raised by Robin could talk very well."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2036, "question": "Many adults in the United States can remember crying the nursery rhyme in the street \"Hot cross buns!\" But only a few people realize this was an early form of advertising. Written advertisements probably began with hieroglyphics more than three thousand years ago, but only a few people could read these symbols. So merchants made signs with pictures or hung their tools over their doors to identify their businesses. In the time of the Roman Empire, wall paintings were a popular form of advertisement. An ad for a play, or some other performance was painted on part of a building or on a wall around a city. People often advertised a house for rent or a freshwater bath in this way, too. Today, large wall signs are still used for outdoor advertising. But outdoor advertising is only a small fracti...\n\nQ: Radio commercials are the best form of advertising because   _  .", "options": ["they can be heard everywhere in a country", "they are cheap and fast", "they are most recently developed", "they can be understood by those who can neither read nor write"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3187, "question": "Dreaming is a natural part of who we are. We explore our dreams and develop personal dreams. We even like to dream BIG! For the most part our dreams and wishes focus on the end result. We see ourselves in love, married, driving a great car, on vacation, with tons of money, in a great career, etc. Dreaming about the end result is just fantasizing and wishing. Wishing relies on some magical force to make our dreams turn into reality, and we become unhappy as we're not living our dreams. So how can we make our dreams come true? That is a question we all often struggle with. Even though we struggle with the answer, the answer is not that clear. We make our dreams come true with the action we take. In my opinion, if you dream about being in good health, then change your dream to see yourself wo...\n\nQ: In order to live our dreams, we must  _  .", "options": ["struggle with dreams day and night.", "have great wishes and thoughts.", "have magical forces every night.", "take action or steps."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2312, "question": "For years, I thought that my mother would become a Centenarian , but after 98 years and eight months, she recently died of old age. As it was with my father, her funeral took place in the most peaceful setting of the countryside of rural Washington County. Even after my father died, we continued to think of our parents as one. They were a team in the traditional sense. Church and family were their life- lines. They worked hard, never complaining. They expected to earn their daily bread by the sweat of their brow. Once during a conversation with Tom Brokaw, who wrote the best- selling hook The Greatest Generation, I told him, \"You left out my parents.\" They didn't go off to war, but they belonged to the Greatest Generation. They, too, were part of the foundation that made America truly grea...\n\nQ: How does the author find his parents?", "options": ["Brave and hardworking.", "Modest and warmhearted.", "Economical and independent.", "Respective and satisfied."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2563, "question": "Black has long been praised for its ability to better women's figures and suit every occasion. But the color has a side-effect--it ages the face. While black does give the appearance of a slimmer figure by making the shadows less visible, wearing it next to the face brings out a negative effect. Black clothing can highlight dark lines under the chin, shadows around the eyes and wrinkles on the face. The effect can be as serious as making women feel exhausted, self-conscious and upset. Wrinkles and sunken areas appear deeper and more pronounced, meaning the effect is more obvious in older women. Dark scarves, hats and high-collared coats are apparently particularly likely to emphasize aging features of the face. But fear not. The effect can be _ by a splash of color around the neck--in the ...\n\nQ: The black dress will be probably suitable for you on condition that there are no   _  .", "options": ["wrinkles on your face", "dark circles around your eyes", "sunken areas that are highlighted", "dark areas or shadows on the face"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1995, "question": "When Carlos Westez died at the age of 76, a language died, too. Westez, more commonly known as Red Thunder Cloud, was the last speaker of the Native American language, Catawba.www.ks5u.com Anyone who wants to hear various songs of the Catawba tribe can get in touch with the Smithsonian Institution in Washington, D.C., where, back in the 1940s, Red Thunder Cloud recorded a series of songs for future generations. They are all that is left of the Catawba language. The language that people used to speak is gone forever. We are all aware of the damage that modern industry can do to the world's ecology. However, few people are aware of the effect that widely spoken languages have on other languages and ways of life. English has spread all over the world. Chinese, Spanish, Russian, and Hindi have...\n\nQ: Why did Westez record songs for the Smithsonian Institution?", "options": ["To fight for Native Americans' rights.", "To deal with the threat of language death.", "To make Native American music popular.", "To help young people learn Catawba songs."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2005, "question": "Several years ago I worked in an office, which had a locust tree growing outside the window. It had grown into a tall tree and must have been there for a long time. The tree blocked the view and made the office seem dull, unfortunately this happened to be the room assigned to me and I was depressed by it for quite some time. When the first spring came, everything was green except the locust tree. Secretly, I was very happy because I had thought it had died. One morning when I opened the window for fresh air, I unexpectedly smelt a familiar sweet scent floating into my office but I couldn't name it. Suddenly, I realized it was the locust tree! The tree that I thought dead was blossoming in full glory. From then on, I usually came to the office very early to see dew forming on the locust tre...\n\nQ: The author of the passage employed a writing way   _  .", "options": ["of holding and releasing", "that released first, then held", "that held first, then released", "that was not holding or releasing"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3457, "question": "I was with a group of businessmen, and we were dealing with a question--What is a good person? At a certain point during the discussion, one of the students--a young man of about thirty--described an event that happened at Christmas. He and his five-year-old son were decorating the Christmas tree, and a little boy came to the front door begging. If you ever visit Mexico, you will see that the people there take begging as nothing to get upset about and nothing to get embarrassed by. So, this little boy came to the door, a boy about the same age as my student's son. The father and the son went to the front door, and the father went back with his five-year-old son and said to him, \"Give him one of your toys.\" At the words, the little boy quickly picked up some toy, and his father said to him,...\n\nQ: From the passage, we can learn that in Mexico   _  .", "options": ["begging is looked down upon", "begging is considered as a normal part of life", "visitors all over the world treat beggars kindly", "few people are living a poor life"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 322, "question": "Now I know that we black people are much more likely to have high blood pressure and diabetes than white people. And _ often lead to heart attacks and other untreated diseases. For example, black people are three to four times more likely than white people to have high blood pressure and twice as likely as the white population to die of a stroke . New research has found out the surprisingly high levels of salt in many of black people's favorite meals. I stopped putting extra salt in my food at the table long ago and I try to cut down on the salt I use in cooking. The recommended daily level of salt for adults is 6 grams. It is easy to see that if you avoid processed foods and use salt in your cooking within the limit, you won't exceed the daily level. The research showed how much salt ther...\n\nQ: What would the writer probably suggest black people do?", "options": ["Order no salad in a restaurant.", "Take in no salt for several days.", "Stop cooking their favorite meals.", "Eat less takeaways."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2232, "question": "Why texting harms your IQ The regular use of text messages and e-mails can lower the IQ more than twice as much as smoking marijuana . That is the statement of researchers who have found that tapping away on a mobile phone or computer keypad or checking for electronic messages temporarily knocks up to 10 points off the user's IQ. This rate of decline in intelligence compares unfavorably with the four-point drop in IQ associated with smoking marijuana, according to British researchers, who have described the phenomenon of improved stupidity as \"infomania\". The research conducted by Hewlett Packard, the technology company, has concluded that it is mainly a problem for adult workers, especially men. It is concluded that too much use of modern technology can damage a person's mind. It can caus...\n\nQ: The research mentioned in the passage is most probably about   _  .", "options": ["the important function of advanced technology", "the damage to one's brain done by unhealthy habits", "the relevance between IQ and use of modern technology", "the relationship between intelligence and working effectiveness"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 229, "question": "He looked like a pirate. With his handkerchief tied in a knot behind his little nine-year-old head, he looked like a pirate, a sad pirate. The first time little David came to our camp, he was hairless and worn out from medical treatments. He was also very angry. Paul Newman's camp counselors ( ) were hoping to fill David's days with fun and laughter. But David stayed inside himself, wanting to be alone, or in a corner of the cabin. At this camp for children with life-threatening illnesses, we had seen some pretty tough children worn out by cancer recover full of energy despite their illness. But we saw little progress in David no matter what we tried with him. Five days into the eight-day session saw a quiet, sad little pirate. Then something happened on that fifth night. Something at camp...\n\nQ: What do you think the theme of the story is?", "options": ["Children with deadly diseases are usually difficult to get along with.", "People should have patience with children with life-threatening illnesses.", "People should tell children with life-threatening illnesses to care nothing about death.", "Love and proper guidance can help people look at something negative in a positive way."], "answer": 3}]